(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T21:09:40.040923",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションが またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering in cards once again!
広がる、ホロライブ！
Expanding Hololive!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2 3月24日(金)発売
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2 Released on Friday, March 24th
ブシロード
Bushiroad
んだんだ 大事ない ちょっと蛹になってやり直すわ
Don't worry, I'll just retreat into my cocoon and start over!
なんて全カイヤ なんだってモヤッて 絶対絶対好きでしょ？
What's going on? What's with this haze? You definitely love it, right?
どうしちゃったの？ 通信 絶対絶対好きでしょ？
What's wrong with this transmission? You definitely love it, right?
now I'm embarrassed now I'm blushing somehow
HOLOLIVE SUPER EXPO 2023 デジタルメッセージボード
[Hololive Super Expo 2023 Digital Message Board]
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade DAY 1
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 グッズラインナップ
[Hololive Super Expo 2023 Merchandise Lineup]
商品ラインナップ
[Product Lineup]
ホロスターズ グッズ
[Holostars Goods]
hololive production Art Collection
ホロライブ 事務所グッズ
[Hololive Office Goods]
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
[Hololive Alternative Goods]
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
[Mangart Beams Collaboration Goods]
holo*27 コラボグッズ
[holo*27 Collaboration Goods]
BUSHIROAD グッズ
[Bushiroad Goods]
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
[Good Smile Company Goods]
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに…
Hololive Production is coming to cards once again...
大集合！
All together!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz is expanding!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack: hololive production Vol.2
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
詳しくは みるハコ で検索！
Check "Miru Hako" for details!
大嫌いな自分に「じゃあね」って言って バイバイバイ やっちおー
Hate myself, say "goodbye" to that, bye-bye-bye, yay
変われちゃう？ きっと変われちゃう？ ねえ素敵じゃない？ ごっこ遊びじゃない
Can I change? Surely I can change? Isn’t it wonderful? It’s not pretend play
どうしちゃったの？ 絶対絶対大好きでしょ
What's wrong? You definitely love it
You are embarrassed right now, let's push it somehow
Our Bright Parade PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 DIGITAL MESSAGE BOARD
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションが、またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is gathering in force on cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
The expanding world of Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack: Hololive Production Vol.2
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
もっと知りたい もっと知りたい
I want to know more, I want to know more,
丸いキズを隠すたびに痛む
it hurts every time I hide the round scar.
だって全開になっちゃってもやめて絶対
Even if I go full throttle, stop, absolutely not—
最愛じゃん
we're dearest to each other, right?
どうしちゃったの 絶好調好き過ぎでしょ
What's got into you? You love being at your best too much!
愛をエンベロープして もう押し込んでサム
Envelope your love and pack it right in...
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を合図に
Shine bright, using our calling voices as a signal!
parade, parade, parade!
探しにいく スタートは何回だって
Going to search, starts can happen any number of times.
ただ独り言を綴った
I just strung together solo words.
ただ始まりたくて走った
I ran just wanting to begin.
遠く暗ガリに灯った
It lit up in the distant darkness.
それは眩し過ぎた名前
That name was far too dazzling.
それは優し過ぎる思い出もずっと
And those memories were far too gentle as well.
近付けと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer.
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, we became bound together.
ほら 今
Look, now
迷子は “僕等” になった
The lost children became "Us".
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright.
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustrations and affection.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
If wind, dreams, and feathers take flight,
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers become light.
終わりなき 兆し
An endless portent.
君を見つけたこと
Finding you
胸を張れるよ
Is something I can be proud of.
ここから これから
From here, from now on
our bright parade, parade!
まだ頼りない予感を
Singing of premonitions that are still unreliable,
歌おう 恥ずかしかなんてないよ
Let's sing, there's nothing to be shy about.
誰にも解けない イマジネーション
An imagination no one can decode,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
A spell so we can meet again someday.
あの日ゼロに始まった ストーリー
A story that started from zero that day.
数え切れない 言の葉
Countless words of leaves,
数え切れない想いじゃないさ
It's not just feelings that can be counted.
ほら 今
Look, now
“僕等”を 一つと呼ぼう
Let's call "Us" as one.
parade, parade, parade!
美しいんだよ
It's so beautiful.
許し合える刹那 夜は きらめく
The fleeting moment of mutual forgiveness makes the night sparkle.
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとなた空
Rain, shine, kaleidoscope, a peerless sky.
相応しい旅路とは 君と在る事さ
A fitting journey is simply being with you.
君と在る事なんだ
It's about existing right by your side.
“ただいま”を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home",
“おかえり”って叫ぶよ
I shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that only natural?
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright.
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
What fills the darkness is you, it's me.
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright.
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustrations and affection.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
If wind, dreams, and feathers take flight,
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers become light.
終わりなき 兆し
An endless portent.
君と飛び込んでいく
Diving in together with you
素敵なスタートさ
Into a wonderful start.
ここから これから
From here, from now on
our bright parade, parade!
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を合図に
Shine bright, using our calling voices as a signal!
parade, parade, parade!
探しにいく スタートは何回だって
Going to search, starts can happen any number of times.
迷子は “僕等” になった
The lost children became "Us".
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright.
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustrations and affection.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
If wind, dreams, and feathers take flight,
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers become light.
終わりなき 兆し
An endless portent.
君を見つけたこと
Finding you
胸を張れるよ
Is something I can be proud of.
ここから これから
From here, from now on
our bright parade, parade!
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
AZKi
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
夜空メル
Yozora Mel
赤井はあと
Akai Haato
癒月ちょこ
Yuzuki Choco
大空スバル
Oozora Subaru
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
沙花叉クロヱ
Sakamata Chloe
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Airani Iofteen
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
一伊那尓栖
Ninomae Ina'nis
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
七詩ムメイ
Nanashi Mumei
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's let our newborn heartbeats resonate!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と また きらめきに乗って
With the best time, the best friends, riding on the sparkle once again!
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember? That very first song
恥ずかしいね まったくこれが震えていた
How embarrassing, looking back, we were shaking all over
あの時から続く未来は みんなと来たんだ ちょうどよかったよ
The future that's continued since that day— I came here with everyone, and it was just right.
もっともっともっともっと加速するハート
A heart accelerating more and more and more!
一緒に行くよどこまでも 歩み的準備はOK
We'll go together anywhere, preparations are OK!
きらけ夢の扉を きらめきライター
Sparkle at the door of dreams, sparkling writer!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best companions!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here wanting to see you, let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ きらめきに乗って
Riding on an endless melody of sparkle!
届いてるかな 私の声
I wonder if my voice is reaching you.
はっきりと届けたいのは 君に笑顔のスマイル
What I clearly want to deliver to you is a smile!
いつものことさ 悔しくって
It's always like this, feeling so frustrated.
みんなとなら笑い出せる
But with everyone, I can start smiling.
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて 全て抱きしめて
Hug me tight, tight, tight, embrace everything!
一緒に行こうどこまでも 歩み的準備はOK
Let's go together anywhere, preparations are OK!
進み続けようこの道を きらめきライター
Let's keep advancing down this road, sparkling writer!
気持ちからすぐに必ず来るから
Feelings will surely come right away.
最高の場所、最高の皆と
In the best place, with the best everyone!
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not an illusion!
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness...
重ねてくハーモニー きらめきまとって
Wearing a sparkling, overlapping harmony!
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing!
そんな願いは我がままでもいいでしょ
Even if such a wish is selfish, that's fine, right?
だって楽しくて止まらない
Because it's too fun to stop!
輝くステージでもっともっと
On the shining stage, more and more!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
It can't be described by just happy, fun, or dear.
今も今もある悩みはあるけど
Even though I still have worries now and then...
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
I'm right here, I'm right here!
君と同じ世界を見つめて みつめて
Gazing at the same world as you, gazing...
きらめきライター 生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Sparkling writer, let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best companions!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here wanting to see you, let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ きらめきに乗って きらめきまとって
Riding on an endless melody of sparkle, wearing sparkle!
「Oh my god」 愛のネタバレ 「別れ」っぽいな
"Oh my god," spoiler for love: "break up" - ish.
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」っぽいな
Spoiler for life: "death" - ish.
なにそれ意味深で かっこいいじゃん…
What's that? So meaningful and cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ 失敬
Dancing with a collection of words like that. Excuse me.
とぅ とぅるる とぅ とぅ るる とぅる "風"
Tu tulu tu tu tulu "ish"
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」ってかんじだな
A spoiler for love, sounds like "breaking up"
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」ってかんじだな
A spoiler for life, sounds like "dying"
なにそれ意味深で かっこいいじゃん…
What's the big meaning behind that? Pretty cool, huh...?
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ 申し訳
Dancing to a collection of buzzwords, excuse me.
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru, "like"
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
Like, like...
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru, "like"
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru...
神っぽいな
Feels like God...
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough, come on.
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなあ
That's enough, that's enough, I'm getting kind of excited.
おっきいね おっきいね 夢
Pretty cheeky, pretty cheeky, dream.
おっきいね おっきいね
Pretty cheeky, pretty cheeky...
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
Business is booming, but class is THE END.
うええい うええい
Uaeei, uaeei...
“Gott ist tot”
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
Feels like God, that's contemptuous.
神っぽいな それ “My God”
Feels like God, that's "My God".
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー IQが下がっていく感じ
Eye-want-you, want-you, IQ is dropping.
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
Feels like malice, that's after all.
邪心っぽいな それ “My God”
Feels like malice, that's "My God".
アイヘイチュー ヘイチュー 害虫はどっちん
Aye-hey-chuu, hey-chuu, which one's the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth.
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup.
アレっぽいな それ 比況
Feels like that, that's a ratio.
アレっぽいな それ
Feels like that, that...
その名言 その意見 その批評
Those catchphrases, those opinions, those reviews.
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, that gag, that sense.
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
Feels like God, that's contemptuous.
ぽいな ぽいな ぽい 憧れちゃう!
Like, like, like, I'm starting to admire it!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru, "like"
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
Like, like...
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru, "like"
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
To-to-ru, to-to-ru, to-to-ru...
神っぽいな
Feels like God...
メタ思考する本質は悪意?
Meta-thinking, is the essence malice?
人を小馬鹿にしたような作為
A contrivance that makes people look foolish.
無為に生き延びるのは難しい
Surviving through inaction is difficult.
権力に呑まれて揺らぐ灯り
A light shaking, swallowed by power.
神を否定し神に成り代わり
Denying God and becoming God instead,
玉座で豹変する小物達
Small fries changing their tune on the throne.
批判に見せかけ自戒の祈り
Disguising criticism as a prayer of self-reproach.
Do you know?
何言ってんの? それ ウザい
What are you even saying? That's annoying.
何言ってんの? それ
What are you even saying? That...
意味がよくわかんないし 眠れちゃうよ マジ
I don't really get the meaning, I'm gonna fall asleep, seriously.
飽きっぽいんだ オーケー
I'm getting sick of it, okay?
みんな飽きっぽいんだ オーケー
Everybody's getting sick of it, okay?
踊れるやつ ちょだいよ ちょだいよ ビーム
Something you can dance to, just a little, just a little beam.
キス hoi ね キス hoi ね それ
Kiss hoi, yeah, kiss hoi, yeah, that.
キス hoi ね キス hoi ね
Kiss hoi, yeah, kiss hoi, yeah.
逆にファンになってきちゃったじゃん
Ended up becoming a fan instead.
ちっちゃいね ちっちゃいね 器
So tiny, so tiny, vessel.
ちっちゃいね ちっちゃいね
So tiny, so tiny...
天才ゆえ孤独ですからね かっけー かっけー…
You're lonely because you're a genius, huh? Cool, cool...
“Gott ist tot”
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
Feels like God, that's contemptuous.
神っぽいな それ “My God”
Feels like God, that's "My God".
超健康 健康 言い張って くたばっていく感じ
Super healthy, healthy, bragging and dragging along.
ヤケっぽいな それ 畢竟
Feels desperate, that's after all.
ヤケっぽいな それ “My God”
Feels desperate, that's "My God".
もう哀愁 哀愁 エピゴーンのヒール
No more pathos, pathos, the heels of the epigon.
そのタイトル その絵 そのストーリー
That title, that drawing, that story.
その音楽 その歌 そのメロディ
That music, that song, that melody.
踏まれたい? お風呂の水欲しい?
Wanna be stepped on? Or want bath water?
本気なの…? 可愛すぎるわ… ほんとヤバすぎ…
For real...?! You're way too cute, seriously too much.
口を開いて? お風呂の水を飲みなさい
Open your mouth and drink that bath water.
踏ん付けて 強く殴ってあげる
Step on me and beat me hard.
みじめな顔してってお願いされても困るし
Even if you ask me to look miserable, cut it out.
あたし冷たい人だよ あたしMof○
I might be mean to you, I'm a mofo.
嫌いじゃ無いでしょ? 見放してあげるから そう…
Don't you hate me? I will let go of you, so...
近づいてきたりするの? いや実際
Though you get closer, no actually,
だってあなたは可愛らしいもの だから許してね お願いね
'cause I think you are sweet, sweet, so please forgive me.
なんちゃって! どーせ期待してたんでしょ?
Just kidding! You thought it'd be like that, right?
ねえ君とのかたちこっとしちゃえ
Let's make something cute with just you and me.
一緒に わお わお 盛り上がってね
Together, wow, wow, let's lift it up!
絶対無理よ暇なんかさっ てっだ ってっだ
I'm not gonna say I have time to spare, really, really.
不安になるし 全然嘘つけないしっ だってだって
I'm getting anxious, I'm totally not lying, really, really.
わっかまっすぐ進むのさっ きらきらもきっともうすぐだしだりだ
I want to go straight ahead, glittering, sparkling, I'm sure it's coming soon.
諦めようなんて言わないでっさっら
I don't want to say "don't give up", come on!
すっとしてなんないしっ だってだって 動いちゃうし
I'm getting sulky, really, really, moving forward.
一歩一歩ちょっとずつ進めば
One step at a time, if we keep going bit by bit,
夢の形どけじゃのっ
it'll be a dream come true, you know.
見たいの僕を君が好きな僕を
I want you to look at me, the me that you like.
ちょっとあまりに見せすぎちゃいなん
I guess I'm showing off a bit too much, huh?
だってさっびっくりするほどできないじゃんまじがって悩んでばっかりじゃん
I mean, I can't really be that surprised, right?
けど君に見つけてほしくて僕は君が無駄に組んだ脱出ならハッピー
I want you to find it in me, 'cause I'm getting tangled up in you.
泣いて泣いておしてしっぽぶって
Don't cry, don't cry, let's end it with a wagging tail.
ための僕をどうか覚えておいても君のすからつこっとしちゃえ
Please remember me, even if you forget me,
どうしようとかたなに持っちゃって沈んだり
Should we do this or that, or sink in a lot of thoughts?
案外行けるかもわふわり浮かんでってもっとだーわん
Can we go beyond that? We're floating, that's what Darwin said.
けっさりがやめられない お座りってそれなんだっけ
You can't just quit easily, you're sitting down, that's why.
うっかりが捕えられない また歩いてぼんにあたるの
You can't just run away, walking right into it.
わんわん吠え安心してるのやめてはいもっと強いで
Stop acting like you're barking, wow, wow, just show me how strong you are!
星がすきみとさいせつりのぼくへと
I want to be with you, the very best me and you.
もっとびっくりがしていまーす
Let's get even more excited.
だってさっびっくりするほどできないじゃんまじがって悩んでばっかりじゃん
I mean, I can't really be that surprised, right?
けど君に見つけてほしくて僕は君が無駄に組んだ脱出ならハッピー
I want you to find it in me, 'cause I'm getting tangled up in you.
だってやっぱり一人じゃだめだって
Right, you can't do it just by yourself,
集まって手をつないではっちゃえば
if we gather around and hold hands, we'll make it!
ring a ding dong ring a ding ding dong
大いなるハッピー
A grand happiness,
パワー炸裂じゃえ
Power bursting forth!
泣いて泣いて愛して深呼吸して
Cry, cry, love, and take a deep breath
パワー炸裂じゃえ
Power bursting forth!
ダメなボクも全部覚えといてほっせ
Remember all of my flaws, too!
キラキラキラなシチュエーション
A sparkling, glittering situation,
欲しい次第さ 浸る気は一切ないぜ
I want it now, no intention of soaking,
とことんメラメラで ぶっちぎる次第で
Blazing all the way, leaving them in the dust,
炸裂に希望願い タイバケーション
Bursting with hope, a tied vacation,
君のすっこころ 作っちゃって いいじゃんハッピーじゃん
Make your heart, isn't it happy?
リンドンリンドン 鼓動が満ちて切たいも着た感じて
Ring-dong, ring-dong, my heart is full, feeling ready,
みんな盛り上がってる? もっと気分上げてけ!
Is everyone hyped up? Raise the vibe even more!
もっともっとエンジョイ 出来ちゃってシーミー
Enjoying even more, able to do it, see me,
上々気分も 重々ホームラン 絶好調の才能 階層キワを
High spirits, a heavy home run, peak condition talent,
見せてあげる ラブリー ポジティブ
I'll show you, lovely, positive,
くるるんくるるん 巻き起こすのだいごく もっとハッピー
Kururun kururun, causing a grand gale, even happier,
どこまでもどこまでもと届けちゃうよ
Reaching out everywhere and anywhere,
そうだろう このロード 時めきタロウ
Isn't that right? This road, heartbeat Taro,
ラララなびき どこまでですか
Lalala fluttering, how far does it go?
ちょっとビビっと感じたら
If you feel a little buzz,
止めらんない 止められない くらい胸のドキドキ ドキ
Can't stop, can't stop, my heart is pounding so much,
一瞬待って 現状進歩 グルグル追いかけっこ
Wait a second, current progress, spinning chase,
アララララ アラモノノー
Arararara, something unusual,
このままいくよ
I'll keep going just like this,
リンドンリンドン 鼓動が満ちて切たいも着た
Ring-dong, ring-dong, my heart is full, ready and dressed,
もっと感じて ジャンプイン ジャンプイン
Feel it more, jump in, jump in,
目をジャンプイン お散歩傷し 世代ライト
Jump in our eyes, walking scars, generation lights,
ハロハロは お見せません
Hello hello, I won't show you,
史上最後の 言葉もインスタ 言えない どこちゃいられない
The very last words on Insta, unable to say,
ずっと見てて ギリギリもしちゃうからキラ
Keep watching me, because I might do it on the edge,
ring dong
真っ直る川 呼びゅんぶんも騒げ プッチヘンブーンと
A straight river, calling and buzzing, make a ruckus,
飛くだけじゃないの そのきんほめての
Not just flying, praise that gold,
伸びてうちょーて あげだんぎゃ あげだんぎゃ 天パレガノマイライフ
Stretching upward, raising it up, natural parade, my life,
やっぱクレイジー びしびしびしきたいえちゃうよ
As expected, crazy, sharply wanting to say it,
君はラブ君はラブ ゆるくアップダウ おかわりは いかがですか
You are love, loosen up and down, would you like seconds?
もっとビビっと感じてよ
Feel the buzz even more,
止めらんない 止められない くらい胸のドキドキ ハック
Can't stop, can't stop, my heart is pounding,
もう一回回って 筋打ってのびの帯
Spin once more, hit the line, stretch the sash,
いつも通り アララララ アラかると
As usual, arararara, a la carte,
そのままいくよ リンドンリンドン 予測不可能な想像以上の少女だから
Ring-dong, ring-dong, because I'm an unpredictable girl,
バンビバンビ 消したモバに おじょうぴしない はげもかよ
Bambi Bambi, erased mobile, don't play around,
喉かなさじゃありません 偶然でっことの 言葉まじちゃう
It's not a peaceful matter, mixing up accidental words,
Yes, Oh Yes なんでもライト 一緒に死んで いかれなサメジ
Yes, Oh Yes, anything is alright, dying together,
人は違う時もあるよ そこがきっといいとこよ
People have different times, that's the good part,
どんな日も 笑顔にするよ 離したくのはいちゃって その笑って頂戴
Making every day smile, want you to smile for me,
笑って頂戴 超々ハッピーニコニコ100万て アララララ ラブアンビ
Super-super happy nico-nico 1 million, arararara,
リンドンリンドン みんな笑う
Ring-dong, ring-dong, everyone smiles,
リンドンリンドン できるはずさ
Ring-dong, ring-dong, you can do it,
リンドンリンドン 聞かせて リンドンと大きな声で
Ring-dong, ring-dong, let me hear it loud,
リンドンリンドン 鼓動が満ちて切たいも着た もっと感じて ジャンプインジャンプイン
Ring-dong, heart is full, feel it, jump in, jump in,
意識おじゃみ ゆるくわたの ハッピネスダノン
Consciousness, loosen up, happiness danon,
ハロハロは お見せません 清楚最後の ダンチョウだから
Hello hello, I won't show you, Commander of purity,
もっともっとラヴ 一緒に死んで いかれなサメジ
More and more love, dying together into crazy shark-ji,
次回もお楽しみに イエーイ!
Look forward to next time, yeah!
リンドンリンドン...
Ring-dong, ring-dong...
[Music]
私ってば全部わかっちゃう
I know everything already,
なんだってテイサイだから
'cause I'm a Seiso idol!
何見てたのか出かけよっか
Let's go see what you were watching!
あそこのかわいい子 ねぇ一体どういうつもり
Hey, what's with that tone?
わかるんだよそういうのって
I get it, you know, stuff like that!
テイサイなんかじゃなくて見てるんだよ絶対
Seiso? No way, I'm watching you!
何度負けたって
No matter how many times I lose,
ずっと待ってるんだタイミング
I'm always waiting for my moment.
目指すはあのスターダム
Aiming for that stardom!
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
働きバチみたい ぶんぶーん
Working like a drone, vroom vroom,
毎日決まったルーティンつまんない
Daily routine is boring.
イケた高級カー Vroom Vroom
A cool, high-end car, vroom vroom.
バーチャルではなくていつかリアルでRide リアルでRide
Not virtual, riding in real life, riding in real life.
誰にも期待されてないけどさ
Nobody's expecting anything from me, but...
Stand up! ネバーネバー give up give up
Stand up! Never, never, give up, give up!
全部全部ぜんぶぜんぶちょうだい
All, all, everything, everything is just fine!
短いライフサイクル 一か八かでダイブ
In this short life cycle, dive in one to eight!
何度負けたって
No matter how many times I lose,
ずっと待ってるんだタイミング
I'm always waiting for my moment.
目指すはあのスターダム
Aiming for that stardom!
Get Chance!! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance!! Unbelievable!
きたる同窓会 Blah Blah
Here comes the reunion, blah blah,
マウント取り合いばっかでつまらない
Just bragging about counts, so boring.
あの子ブランドバック ぶらぶら
That girl's designer bag, drag drag.
自分を着飾るよりも中身で勝負 中身で勝負
Winning with substance rather than dressing up.
誰にも期待されてないけどさ
Nobody's expecting anything from me, but...
頭ぐるぐるネガティブ
My head is spinning with negativity.
自分にしかきっとできないこと
Something only I can do.
Stand up! ネバーネバー give up give up
Stand up! Never, never, give up, give up!
全部全部ぜんぶぜんぶちょうだい
All, all, everything, everything is just fine!
私ってば何でもできちゃう
I know everything already,
なんだってテイサイだから
'cause I'm a Seiso idol!
どこにいるか出かけよっか
Let's go see where you are!
君の後ろ
Behind you!
ほらやっぱり隠してたじゃん
See, you're hiding your phone again!
女の子と話したいとか嘘ばっか
You wanna talk to girls or lie or what?
話してよどうしないの？既読してIn the chat!
Explain yourself! No way, I'm checking your chat!
何度負けたって
No matter how many times I lose,
ずっと待ってるんだタイミング
I'm always waiting for my moment.
もう１回目を離すとこれなくなるから
If you make me wait one more time, I'm walking away!
聞いてるの？
Are you listening?
待てないのさ待たされてたんだ
I've been made to wait so many times.
２回目じゃないのわからないの
I don't even know how it feels anymore.
新しい愛なら一目惚れ
If it's new love, it's love at first sight.
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
走り続けてきてのりずむ
Keep running with this rhythm,
掴み取れるわ迷う世界を
And the shining world is waiting for me to step in!
抱きしめて 胸は震えるくらい
Hold me tight, my heart is trembling,
おかしくしちゃうよ
Let's go crazy together!
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
走り続けてきてのりずむ
Keep running with this rhythm,
掴み取れるわ迷う世界を
And the shining world is waiting for me to step in!
抱きしめて 胸は震えるくらい
Hold me tight, my heart is trembling,
おかしくしちゃうよ
Let's go crazy together!
新しい愛なら一目惚れ
If it's new love, it's love at first sight.
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
走り続けてきてのりずむ
Keep running with this rhythm,
掴み取れるわ迷う世界を
And the shining world is waiting for me to step in!
抱きしめて 胸は震えるくらい
Hold me tight, my heart is trembling,
おかしくしちゃうよ
Let's go crazy together!
わかってるよ
I know everything,
君だけの風
It's just you and me.
その目がすべてなんだよね
The only thing that matters is you.
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
走り続けてきてのりずむ
Keep running with this rhythm,
掴み取れるわ迷う世界を
And the shining world is waiting for me to step in!
抱きしめて 胸は震えるくらい
Hold me tight, my heart is trembling,
おかしくしちゃうよ
Let's go crazy together!
Get Chance! アンビリーバブル
Get Chance! Unbelievable!
走り続けてきてのりずむ
Keep running with this rhythm,
掴み取れるわ迷う世界を
And the shining world is waiting for me to step in!
抱きしめて 胸は震えるくらい
Hold me tight, my heart is trembling,
おかしくしちゃうよ
Let's go crazy together!
果てしない愛
There's no end to this love,
止まらないよ 離れないよ
Shining so bright, never apart!
見るのことちゃんと見てくれてた？
Did you watch me the whole time?
見てくれてありがとう
Thank you.
これからはもっとずっと傍にいてね
From now on, stay right by my side, okay?
大好き！
I love you!
[Music]
世界で一番おひめさま
The world's number one princess!
そういう扱い心得てよね
Treat me just like that, got it?
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気付くこと
First: notice when I change my hair.
その二 ちゃんと靴まで見ること いいね?
Second: look all the way down to my shoes, okay?
その三 わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Third: reply with three words to every word I say.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
Got it? Make sure my right hand isn't empty!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思って欲しいの かわいいって
I just want you to truly adore me!
世界で一番おひめさま
The world's number one princess!
気が付いて ねぇねぇ
Pay attention to me, hey, hey!
待たせるなんて論外よ
Making me wait is completely out of the question!
わたしを誰だと思ってるの?
Who do you think I am?
もう何だか あまいものが食べたい!
I want something sweet right now!
欠点? かわいいの間違いでしょん
Flaws? You must mean "cute"!
ねぇねぇ? 私の話ちゃんと聞いてる? ちょっと······
Hey, hey, are you actually listening to me?
あ、それとね? 白いうお馬さん 決まってるでしょ?
Oh, and you know? A white horse, obviously!
迎えに来て
Come pick me up.
わかったらかしずいて 手を取って“おひめさま”って
Got it? Just take my hand and call me "Princess"!
別に わがままなんて言ってないんだから
Not that I'm being selfish,
でもね 少しぐらい褒めてくれたっていいのよ?
Though, a little pampering would be nice.
世界でわたしだけのおうじさま
The world's only prince for me!
気が付いて ほらほら おててが空いています
Wake up and look, hey, my hands are empty!
無口で無愛想なおうじさま もう どうして!
You clueless, loveless prince, why won't you notice me?
気が付いてよ早く
Notice me sooner!
みんな みんな 我慢します...
Everyone is being so patient...
世界で一番おひめさま
The world's number one princess!
背は高い方がいいけど そんなタイプじゃなかったの
I wanted someone tall, but he wasn't really that type.
気難しそうな感じ…どっちかって言って ゆううつ通りだったかな
He seemed difficult... if anything, just as gloomy as I thought.
話すと全然違ってて 笑うと目が子供みたいで
When we talk, he's totally different, and when he smiles, his eyes look like a child's.
クシャクシャになっちゃう目元
His eyes crinkling up...
なんかにすごいドキッとしたりして
makes my heart flutter so much...
でも…なんでホントのこと言っちゃうバカなの?
But... why is he such a fool to tell the truth?
最初は「彼女いないよ」って ウソつくのが礼儀でしょ普通
Usually, the polite lie is saying "I don't have a girlfriend" at first.
そうよ…なんでこんなフラれた気分な?
That's right... why do I feel like I've been dumped?
夢見る前から叶わない 恋って気付いちゃいじまったじゃない
Even before dreaming, I realized I'd fallen in love—it's impossible.
大好きになった…どうしよう まだ出会ったばかりなんだけれど
I've come to love him... what should I do? We've only just met,
切ない気持ちが溢れてきて 胸がキュンってなってるよ
but a bittersweet feeling overflows, and my heart is aching.
そうよ…大好きなんだ…どうにもこうにも すごいことになってきたよ
That's right... I love him so much... things have gotten incredible.
会いたい気持ちで頭の中 ふわふわ?ってなってるよ
With feelings of wanting to see him, my head is all fuzzy.
手をつないで離さないで 見つめ合って抱きしめ合って
Holding hands and never letting go, gazing at each other, hugging tightly,
キスし合って髪を触って いつまでもずっとこうしてて
kissing and touching each other's hair, let's stay like this forever.
「甘いものが好き!」って盛り上がって 「食べに行こうよ?」なんてなって
Getting excited about "I love sweets!" and "Let's go eat some?"
「ランチならまあいっか…」って なんか…ありがちな感じだね
And "Well, lunch is fine..." It feels kind of cliché.
ビュッフェの列に並んでたの 普通に話してるんだけど
We were standing in line at the buffet, talking normally,
顔近すぎでしょ!またなんか 意味なくドキッとしたりして
but your face is way too close! Once again, my heart flutters for no reason.
「ピアス…これいいね…」って 褒められて舞い上がった
When you praised my earrings ("These are nice..."), I was ecstatic.
けど…「彼女にも見せてあげよう」って 写メ撮られる…ってこれどうなの?
But then you say "I'll show them to my girlfriend too" and take a photo... What is this?!
そうよ…なんでこんなミジメな気分な?
That's right... why do I feel so miserable?
戦うことすら出来ないバリア 張られちゃってんの?
Have you put up a barrier where I can't even fight?
大好きになった…どうしよう 見つめ合ったばかりなんだけれど
I've come to love him... what should I do? We've only just started gazing at each other,
悲しい気持ちが溢れてきて 胸がキュンってなってるよ
but a sad feeling overflows, and my heart is aching.
そうよ…なんだかんだか止まらなくなっちゃったかも
That's right... maybe I couldn't stop myself anymore.
いけない妄想で 体中ふわふわ ってなってるよ
With sinful delusions, my whole body is all fluffy.
手をつないで離さないで 見つめ合って抱きしめ合って
Holding hands and never letting go, gazing at each other, hugging tightly,
キスし合って髪を触って いつまでもずっとこうしてて
kissing and touching each other's hair, let's stay like this forever.
もしも願いが叶うなら 出会いのリセットボタンを押させて
If my wish could come true, let me press the reset button on our meeting.
そうよ神様!このバカな彼が
That's right, God! This foolish guy...
まだ自己紹介終わってないからね！
We haven't finished our self-introductions yet!
そうだな、名乗らないとですね！
That's right, we have to introduce ourselves!
そうですよ、じゃあ団長から名乗ります！
That's right! So, Captain will go first!
よろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well!
はーい！みなさん！こんます！
Hiii! Everyone! Konmas!
あ、白銀ノエルのこのライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと
Ah, Shirogane Noel for this live, as the 3rd gen Shirogane Noel...
はーいみなさん！こんこよー！
Hii everyone! Konkoyo!
holoライブ6期生の…！
Hololive 6th gen...
holoライブ4th fes. Our Bright Paradeのいよいよ始まります！
Hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade is finally starting!
あー、目がまた…大丈夫ですか？
Ah, my eyes again... are you okay?
もう本当に緊張して！
I'm already so nervous!
いや、そうだよね。だってほら、こよちゃん、初めてじゃない？全体ライブ。
Yeah, that's true. I mean, look, Koyori-chan, isn't this your first overall live?
全体ライブもだし、お客様がいるっていうのも初めてなので、もう、しかもね声出しオッケーですからみんな声本当にありがとうございます！
Not only is it an overall live, but it's also my first time having an audience. Plus, cheering is allowed, so thank you all so much for your voices!
いっぱいありがとね！
Thank you so much!
幸せだー！
I'm so happy!
すごいね！
Amazing!
え、ちょっとノエル先輩、こゆりやりたいことあるんですけど。
Um, Noel-senpai, Koyori has something she wants to do.
あれの、いやいいですか？悔いなくね、全部やっちゃおう！やっていいですか？いいよ！
Is that okay? Let's do it all without regrets! Can I do it? Sure!
いや、やっぱりね、声が出せるということなので、皆さんもね声出す練習もっともっとしないといけないと思うので、コール＆レスポンスしていきませんか？
Well, since we can use our voices, I think everyone needs to practice voicing out more, so shall we do a call and response?
やるぞー！
Let's do it!
じゃあ、先輩お手本お願いします！ え、任かせてよ！
Well then, Senpai, please give us an example! Leave it to me!
じゃあ、みんな！ アリーナの人声出して手を振れ！
Well then, everyone! People in the arena, raise your voices and wave your hands!
それじゃあ、2回戦きー！
Now then, round two!
3階席！
3rd floor seats!
見えてるよー！
We can see you!
そして そしてね油断してる 現地組だけかと思いきや 配信のみんなも見えてるよ！
And also, you know, we thought it was just the in-person attendees, but we can see everyone streaming too!
配信！
Streaming audience!
みんな！イエーイ！
Everyone! Yay!
みんなも元気ですね！
Everyone has great energy too!
ねー！
Yeah!
他のもどうですか？聞きたい！
How about the others? I want to hear!
じゃあいいですか？
Alright, is that okay?
男の子！いますかー！
Boys! Are you here?!
男の子ー！イエーイ！
Boys! Yay!
じゃあ、女の子ー！
Now, girls!
結構ね、あのカメラにも映ってましたからね。始まる前も。
It was showing up on the cameras quite a bit, even before it started.
じゃあ、行きましょう！どっちでもない人！
Now, let's go! People who are neither!
じゃあ、関東・近畿から来たよって人！
Now, people who came from Kanto or Kinki!
多いですね！
There are a lot!
でもなんか上げてない人もいるし。
Though some people didn't raise their hands.
じゃあ、関東以外から来たよって人！
Now, people who came from outside Kanto!
海外に！いますかー！
Overseas! Are you here?!
オーシーズ！オーシーズガイズ！いるいる！
Overseas! Overseas guys! They're here!
ありがとうございます！気をつけて帰ってね！
Thank you very much! Be careful on your way back!
いやー、嬉しいですね！すごいね。
Man, I'm so happy! That's amazing.
じゃあ、ちょっと言葉も言ってもらいたいんですが。
Now, we'd like you to say some words too.
今夜の、下の名前は、なにー！
Tonight's first name is, what?!
嬉しい！うれしい！うれしい！
I'm happy! Happy! Happy!
じゃ、団長の名前はー！
Then, the leader's name is!
ナイス！朝ご飯何食べたー！
Nice! What did you eat for breakfast?!
いやちょっと分からな、楽しすぎてさ！なんかずっとやりたいんだけど。
I don't know, it's just too fun! I kinda want to keep doing this.
ちょっとね、やっぱり、時間限られてるから。
Well, you know, time is limited after all.
ちょっとね、おしらせです。
Now, it's an announcement.
今回のハッシュタグ、皆さん覚えてますか？
Do you all remember the hashtag for this time?
広がるホロライブDAY1です！
It's Hirogaru Hololive DAY1!
スクショとかもオッケーなので！
Screenshots are also fine, so!
YouTubeで無料チラ見せを見ている方は！
For those watching the free preview on YouTube!
ご覧の方ここまでとなります！
Viewers, this is where it ends!
はい、見たいという方はぜひ概要欄から配信サイトに飛んでチケットのお買い求めお願いいたします！
Yes, for those who want to watch, please go to the streaming site from the description and purchase a ticket!
なごり惜しいけど行きますか、寂しい。
It's bittersweet, but shall we go? I'm sad.
この後も楽しんでくださいね！
Please enjoy the rest as well!
せーの！広がるホロライブ！
Ready, go! Hirogaru Hololive!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion has ended! Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！